<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Getting Started on WTF - the terminal dashboard</title>
    <link>https://wtfutil.com/getting_started/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Getting Started on WTF - the terminal dashboard</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 16:11:58 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://wtfutil.com/getting_started/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Installation</title>
      <link>https://wtfutil.com/getting_started/installation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 09:59:40 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wtfutil.com/getting_started/installation/</guid>
      <description>Homebrew brew tap wtfutil/wtfutil brew install wtfutil wtfutil As a Binary Grab the latest version from here:
https://github.com/wtfutil/wtf/releases expand it, and cd into the resulting directory. Then run:
./wtfutil and that should also do it.
From Source Download the source code repo and install the dependencies:
# Set the Go proxy variable to GoCenter export GOPROXY=&amp;#34;https://gocenter.io&amp;#34; # Enable Go modules export GO111MODULE=on go get -u github.com/wtfutil/wtf cd $GOPATH/src/github.com/wtfutil/wtf make install make run and that should do it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uninstallation</title>
      <link>https://wtfutil.com/getting_started/uninstall/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2018 09:59:40 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wtfutil.com/getting_started/uninstall/</guid>
      <description>Homebrew brew uninstall wtfutil Remove the Binary and Configuration WTF ships as a single binary named wtfutil. Assuming you have installed the binary, run:
rm $(which wtfutil) If you have configured WTF, you will also want to delete your configs:
rm ~/.config/wtf and that should also do it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Glossary</title>
      <link>https://wtfutil.com/getting_started/glossary/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 12:34:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wtfutil.com/getting_started/glossary/</guid>
      <description>Module A discrete unit of data collection and display. A data interface concept. A package inside the app.
Examples: New Relic, Git, Weather.
Widget The onscreen representation of a Module. The widget is responsible for being the interface between the app and the data collection.
Widgets are defined by a required widget.go file in a Module.
WTF An acronym for &amp;ldquo;What The Fsck?&amp;rdquo;, as in &amp;ldquo;What the fsck are all these browser tabs open for?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>