<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto Currencies on WTF - the terminal dashboard</title>
    <link>https://wtfutil.com/modules/cryptocurrencies/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Crypto Currencies on WTF - the terminal dashboard</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 May 2018 18:04:58 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://wtfutil.com/modules/cryptocurrencies/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bittrex</title>
      <link>https://wtfutil.com/modules/cryptocurrencies/bittrex/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 20:06:40 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wtfutil.com/modules/cryptocurrencies/bittrex/</guid>
      <description>Get the last 24 hour summary of cryptocurrencies market using Bittrex.
Configuration Copy   bittrex: colors: base: name: orange displayName: red market: name: red field: white value: green enabled: true position: top: -2 left: 2 height: 3 width: 1 refreshInterval: 5 summary: BTC: displayName: Bitcoin market: - LTC - ETH    Screenshots Attributes   Name Description Value    border Optional Whether or not to draw this widget with a border.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blockfolio</title>
      <link>https://wtfutil.com/modules/cryptocurrencies/blockfolio/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 09:29:59 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wtfutil.com/modules/cryptocurrencies/blockfolio/</guid>
      <description>Display your Blockfolio crypto holdings.
Configuration Copy   blockfolio: colors: name: blue grows: green drop: red device_token: &amp;#34;device token&amp;#34; displayHoldings: true enabled: true position: top: 3 left: 1 width: 1 height: 1 refreshInterval: 400    Screenshots Attributes   Name Description Value    border Optional Whether or not to draw this widget with a border. Default: true. true, false   colors.drop  Any X11 color name or long-form hex value (i.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CryptoLive</title>
      <link>https://wtfutil.com/modules/cryptocurrencies/cryptolive/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2018 20:06:40 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wtfutil.com/modules/cryptocurrencies/cryptolive/</guid>
      <description>Compare crypto currencies using CryptoCompare.
Configuration Copy   cryptolive: enabled: true position: top: 5 left: 2 height: 1 width: 2 updateInterval: 15 currencies: BTC: displayName: Bitcoin to: - USD - EUR - ETH - LTC - DOGE LTC: displayName: Ethereum to: - USD - EUR - BTC top: BTC: displayName: Bitcoin limit: 5 to: - USD colors: from: name: coral displayName: grey to: name: white price: green top: from: name: grey displayName: coral to: name: red field: white value: green    Screenshots Attributes   Name Description Value    border Optional Whether or not to draw this widget with a border.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
